Subtitles by Obscuritron
Sometimes the past should be left a memory .
To gather dust within the cupboards of recorded time .
- He 's very heavy . - Yes .
Is there any man who can satisfy me ?
Return the kris to it 's former form and give it back to me .
You are my wife now , I want you to stop the killings .
Give me that !
Bastard ! You 've tricked me !
In one-hundred years I 'll have my revenge on your great granddaughter .
I will go to the bottom of the sea -
and join forces with the powers of evil .
I shall return and avenge this insult .
Excuse me .
I 'm looking for a book on the legend of the South Sea Queen .
The " South Sea Queen " ?
What do you want it for ?
I 'm working on a thesis .
You see , there was this story about a castle that sank under the sea .
And a kris that was said to have mystical powers ?
Yes , exactly .
You have the book ?
I 've looked everywhere . I hope you have it .
I might .
Let me see .
Not so fast . Do you know what you 're in for ?
Whoever finds the secret of the South Sea Queen -
will live in great danger of her soul .
Do you understand ?
Come on !
In this day and age , you speak of legends ?
I 'm an anthropologist .
What is in this book -
may bring you to a fate -
worse than anything -
you could imagine .
And what is that ?
The unknown .
Well ... Maybe it 's not for your after all .
Let 's see it .
Beware
of the South Sea Queen .
That old man gave me the creeps -
but if I don 't finish my thesis , I don 't graduate .
So let 's just get on with it .
All right you old pirate , what is it now ?
Are you sure you wanna go there ?
It 's not an everyday tourist trap .
There are a lot of sharks in that area .
I can take you to a better place for diving .
You know ...
I 've been waiting a long time for this .
Just forget that place , lady .
What do you mean , forget it ?
This is the reason I 've come here .
To find out about the South Sea Queen .
Are you out of your mind , lady ?
I 'm not taking you there .
Will you stop calling me lady ?
I 'm not a lady , I 'm an anthropologist .
You won 't wanna go there .
Oh , yes I will .
The book says that 's where I have to go .
Oh no , not that again .
According to the legend , the queen walked into the sea .
And then the castle sank , but nobody ever heard of the kris again .
What a load of shit ...
There 's a castle under the sea around here somewhere .
And this kris , this dagger , must be down there inside it .
I 've got to find it .
Come on .
You don 't wanna believe that .
It 's a bloody legend .
Yes , but it 's true .
You read too much .
Bloody woman ...
What then ? Are you afraid ?
You said it 's only a legend .
Pop-eye .
Shut off the engine .
Aye aye , captain .
Look , girl ...
This is as far as I 'm taking you .
Come on .
You knew I was gonna go there .
People told me you 've been to that place .
People are building space stations on the moon , you know ?
What makes you so superstitious anyway ?
Talk to me , captain .
You don 't know how many people disappeared .
Superstition , huh .
What the hell do you know ?
They go , and never come back .
The Sea Queen ...
She took them all .
Their bodies , too .
Now ...
You still wanna go there ?
His brother disappeared that way .
Don 't worry , it 'll be all right .
Couldn 't we just pass by it ?
Yeah ...
Maybe I 'm really a silly old fool .
Please ? I 'll be good , promise .
Pop-eye !
Turn on the engine .
Let 's go .
- I 'm gonna regret this . - Don 't be such an old woman .
Over there .
One hundred years ago there was a volcano that blew up the whole island .
Right there , just blew it away .
Depth gauge , regulator , compass ...
All set .
- Okay ? - Okay , wish me luck .
Tania ? What happened ?
My aqualung isn 't working properly .
Let me check something .
That should do it .
Get your goggles on now .
The hell 's taking her so long ?
Her oxygen is almost gone .
What the ...
Oh my god , what have I done ? !
Fuckin ' Saturday night on the beach !
Handsome guy like me .. !
Shit .. !
If you are handsome , there is hope for every monkey in Java !
Thanks , asshole !
And fuck you , too !
Oh god , I need a woman .. !
Hey , remember the lecture of the South Sea Queen ?
Wouldn 't it be nice if she could come now ?
Hey look , there is a naked woman coming .
Crazy tourists !
Go on . You 're not gonna catch AIDS .
Wanna - - wanna have a good time ?
I got some pot in the car .
Hey . Hey !
Hey . Hey ! How about a threesome ?
Wait your turn .
Sloppy seconds ...
I can 't believe this shit .
Damn , she 's bad .
Now let 's - -
Wants her now ?
- That 's affirmative , wrap it up and come on in . - Hey , check out this action .
Okay , we 're up in the penthouse right now , we 're gonna wrap it up and ... listen .
Roger needs to go down the hall here and then we 're just gonna come on back - -
What the - - that room is supposed to be locked ?
All kinds of things happen on the graveyard shift .
Pete , go check room 1113 .
Over .
- Evening , what are you having ? - Beer .
Don 't you all get shit-faced drunk now , do you hear ?
I just want me a couple of beers .
Hey , you serve beer here or just milk ?
Say , there 's a pretty face .
You too , pretty face . What are you having ?
Would be a sin to pass you up .
No thanks , I don 't think so .
Don 't be silly sweetheart , I just wanna show you a good time .
Here , you wanna feel it first ?
Hi , asshole .
Have a nice day !
- You okay ? - Wow .
That 's what I call police brutality , man .
Hey Snake , I 'm not on duty , man . I never pulled out my badge .
Furthermore , those guys deserved it . Hey Tub , where 's Joe ?
He 's still on a mission .
Let 's go and get a drink , Snake .
- Who were those two ... - We should have intervened earlier -
before those punks started bothering you .
- Max McNeil . - Linda .
Why Max , you 're blushing .
I won 't bite ...
- Max ! - Hm ?
We got a triple homicide with the same M.O.
Where are the bodies ?
They 're over at the morgue .
- I got the autopsy reports . - We 'll read them on the way .
- Anything to eat ? - Just hot dogs .
I really hate hot dogs .
Listen , Jack and I have seen more dead bodies than you 've eaten hot dogs .
So shut up and eat .
- Boy , am I glad that is over ... - You know what , I have a date tonight .
- Bye ! - My arm 's so skinny .
There she is . Erica . Erica !
Oh no , not another interview , Maryann .
My , nice necklace .
- Jill Petersen from channel 6 . - Hi Jill .
Won 't take a minute , okay ?
Well ...
Erica , what makes your show such a hit ?
I don 't know .
Because you 've got such a sexy body !
No , they probably like the show .
Okay . I 've heard that you got an offer from J-Town Records .
My manager just told me yesterday .
Aren 't you excited ?
I am . Wouldn 't you be ?
Well , I hope you 'll be famous soon .
I don 't know .
I can 't imagine being ... famous .
I just wanna have a simple life .
I think I 'm just ... too excited and nervous -
about the whole thing .
All that glamor and glitter is just not for me .
- Okay , good luck on the show . Bye now . - Thanks , I 'll need it .
Well , I 'm sure you 've all met Erica .
A sweet girl who is going to be doing a rock show tonight .
I 'm Jill Petersen for channel 6 .
Back to you , Jack .
American Express is after my blood again , all my checks are bouncing like yoyo 's .
You 've got to stop all this compulsive buying , how are you going to pay your tuition ?
Don 't be so boring .
What 's the point of not having money if you can 't spend it ?
Besides , you should talk , you 're on your way to fame and fortune .
I was just lucky .
Oh yeah ?
Do you see how those people look at you ? You really are famous .
Hey .. !
- I don 't know , I can imagine being famous - Hey , cut that out , will ya ?
Stop teasing me .
Erica .
Look , that 's what I was telling you about .
Yeah , that 's the one .
That 's an authentic reproduction . $ 67,90 .
Do you like it ?
- Mm-hmm . - Really ?
Mm , yeah .
Hey , you know , yours look more shiny than mine .
- Of course , mine is an antique one . - Thank you .
Great-grandpa Elias gave it to me .
Big deal .
Wow , there goes my allowance for this week .
Hey , you 'll still remember me when you 're famous , right ?
Of course , you silly .. !
Oh , it 's getting a bit late . Tell you what .
- I 'm gonna go to rehearsal now . - Okay , break a leg !
- Okay Maryann , see you tonight at the pub . - Bye bye .
El-e-ka !
Okay . Last case today , gentlemen .
We have three very dead bodies here .
These two were found on the beach yesterday .
This one was found last night .
He 's a hotel security guard . Let 's have a look , shall we ?
- Doesn 't look very happy now , does he ? - Very interesting .
It says here all three of these guys died with their cocks bitten off .
Could be a small animal .
The report say an eel .
An eel ?
On dry land ?
I 've heard of the ultimate blow job , but ...
- This is too much . - Obviously done by the same person .
But why ? What 's his or her motive ?
- How can a human being do this ? - Oh , very easily .
- First you take their pants off - - - Yeah okay , cut it out .
I don 't wanna know about it .
Back to business , gentlemen .
Tom , I want you to check out the scene of the crime first thing tomorrow morning .
I 'll do it tonight .
Tom , it 's almost midnight .
- Take a break . - Yeah !
Let 's go to the pub , all work and no play ,
Nah , you take Max to the pub .
I 'll tell you what I find out tomorrow morning at 07 : 00 .
Okay , gentlemen ?
- See you . - Yo .
All right .
But you 'll miss a good time .
Yeah , some of us have to work for a living .
Hey , why the hell isn 't this closed ?
What for ?
- He 's not gonna get away , man . - That 's disgusting .
It 's good , man .
Put these turkey 's back in the ice box .
They 're starting to get ripe .
Yeah , yeah ...
Cute , isn 't she ?
Mm .
Yeah .
You don 't see anyone like that very often .
Jack .
Stop trying to get me involved , will ya ?
Stop living in the past man , it 's all over .
Damn it , I 'm trying .
I 'm just not ready yet , okay ?
Okay , but half of the girls at the office -
are beginning to think that you 're gay .
Thank you . Thank you so much .
Let 's go , this way !
- Jack , cover me , I 'll take the girl . - Okay , this way .
Quick , let 's get out of here now !
- Come with me if you want to live . - Let 's move !
- Stop , my high heels ! - Shut up and run !
- Max , you go first . - You got it .
Jack !
- Wait , wait - - - Forget the goddam shoe .
This way .
Get in the car .
MC-1 calling station , over .
Did you see that ? Why didn 't she die ?
How the hell should I know ?
You tell me .
Mr. Bigshot .. !
Where are you taking me ?
- Now , what 's best for security - - - Who are you anyway ?
- You stop the car - - - Will you just shut up ? !
Don 't you dare yell at me !
I 'll yell whenever I wanna .
MC-1 calling station , over .
Come on ... MC-1 calling station , over !
I didn 't mean to shout at you .
You didn 't even say sorry .
This is MC-1 , where the hell were you guys ?
I needed a backup .
Sorry man , it 's just we had news of a shootout at the Manhattan pub .
I was there , dammit , and Jack bought it .
Now , where is Tom ?
Tell him to get off his ass .
I sent him out to check on a homicide .
Also , one of our cars is missing .
10-4 , what 's your location ?
Going east on 56th street , toward Newmarket .
MC-1 out .
10-4 , over and out .
I wanna go home .
Okay .
Backup is coming .
They 'll take you home .
Get down !
Run !
Take the wheel , I 'm gonna have some fun .
- Hey , asshole ! - Quick , try the handbrake .
We got her now .
- Christ , it 's empty . - Shit !
Where did she go ?
Are you all right ?
Yeah , just a few scratches .
Jack bought it .
Yes , we know .
I 'm sorry .
Let 's go .
Max , follow me .
I got to show you something .
- Sergeant Betty ? - Yes , sir ?
Would you take Erica to get some clean clothes , please ?
Okay , please come with me .
We checked out our files according to your description .
Sergeant Pono .
Can you find the immigration 's file on the suspect ?
Yes , sir .
You wouldn 't believe this .
After tonight I 'll believe anything .
A lot of tourists this time of year .
We found this in the missing persons report .
She ... disappeared three days ago on a fishing trip .
And that 's not all .
The damnedest thing about her was there was no trace of the boat or the crew .
Max , you 're called to the states .
Hi Tub .
Hi buddy , you sound terrible ?
It 's been a long day .
My man , what 's happening ?
- Come on over , we 're partying . - Snake , you 're stoned again .
Buddy , tell us what 's happening over there .
Some strange woman starts shooting up people .
And you won 't believe this ...
She can 't be killed .
Whatcha ' mean ?
If it bleeds , it dies .
Call Joe for me .
Tell him I need help .
I gotta go .
See ya .
Right Max , we 're on our way .
Max ?
And old man wants to see Erica .
- In there . - Let 's go .
Who is he ?
Masabu !
There , there , there ...
Maryann 's dead .
I know , I know , I know .
I saw it on the news .
I know , yes .
I knew this thing was going to happen .
Since the time I talked to you last week .
You 're the one she 's after .
Give me the necklace .
That evil is using this to track you down .
What evil ?
That woman cannot die .
Because she has the spirit of the South Sea Queen .
Your great grandfather Elias -
was the one-hundredth husband of the evil queen .
I heard about that .
So the legend is true after all , huh ?
It took the queen 's vital force .
She swore to avenge herself .
I 'm sorry , I don 't think I can believe that .
Max ?
- Excuse me . - Don 't go - -
He hasn 't been in our country very long .
- If this report ... - Max !
The old man was telling the truth .
You should believe in it .
Not me .
This kris is from your great grandfather Elias .
You are his last and only descendant .
He wanted you to keep it .
He made me promise to watch out for the South Sea Queen .
And
I have waited for 50 years .
And then , last night I had a dream .
I dreamed that the sea was on fire .
So I knew ...
The South Sea Queen has reincarnated .
But don 't worry .
I 'll protect you .
- Hey , stop ! - Halt !
- Let 's go ! - Move , move !
- Look , my paycheck is $ 50 short . - It 's there , sir .
Just sign .
Wake up Pono , we 've got an alert .
Where is Erica ?
Where ?
Okay , look out !
Cover me !
- Get in there ! - Back here !
- Take her down ! - I 'll get her .
Kill her , dammit !
Up here .
What the hell is going on ?
I know I hit her point blank .
- Betty , get out of here ! - Go !
Now !
Steve , we 've got a problem .
You two , cover the computer room . Go !
- This way . - Right .
Damn , she got Betty !
- Don 't go . - Stay her .
Where are you going ?
I 'm going to fight this evil .
If I die ...
Keep the kris .
People are weak , and may fail .
But this ...
This you can trust .
What 's going on ?
- It 's unbelievable . - Beats the hell outta me .
Jesus Christ .. !
Go and get Erica outta here !
Go ! Go !
It 's okay Erica , it 's me .
- Where 's Max ? - Coming .
It 's only you .
Where 's Masabu ?
He 's dead .
- Oh my god . - Let 's go .
Go and aid Erica !
Bitch , you - -
Pop the hood .
This car is not gonna make it .
We 'll have to do it on foot .
Better find a place to crash .
That way .
You 're not cold , are you ?
I 'm freezing .. !
Look , here .
Take my coat .
Thanks .
We gotta do something about that .
Doesn 't it hurt ?
Nah .
You don 't say much .
Are your parents still alive ?
Are you married ?
I was .
She died .
I 'm sorry .
Tell me about her .
Please ?
Not much to tell .
Five years ago , she asked me to quit my job as a cop .
Move to Minnesota and open a restaurant .
She was right .
Raped and murdered by an ex-con ...
Bastard .. !
Could 've happen to anybody .
But it had to happen to her .
It 's all my fault .
It doesn 't make a difference anymore .
I haven 't talked so much in years .
Wh - - what 's the matter ?
Nothing .
My parents died .
When I was about seven .
I was brought up by my uncle Abu .
Now he 's gone .. !
Maryann was
my best friend .
Now she 's gone too .
Everybody 's gone .
God , I 'm alone .
- It will all look better in the morning . - Damn you !
Can 't you see I 'm crying for you ?
Good morning .
I got your breakfast , ma 'am .
Come in .
I wish great grandpa hadn 't been to that place , life would 've been much easier for me .
Don 't worry baby , it 'll work out all right .
Hope so .
- Hey , I 'll get something to eat , all right ? - And I 'll use the phone .
- Special security . - Tommy ?
- Max ! - Are you still alive ?
Sure .
You think a freakin ' witch like that could kill me ?
Uh-uh , no way .
What 's the situation ?
Well , the headquarters is a mess , but I 've called for help from the states .
Joe , Snake and Tub are on their way over .
Why don 't you meet us at the old abandoned airport ?
You got that , Max ?
- Shit , Erica ! - Max ?
Max , are you still there ?
This way !
Get down ! Get down !
- Look out ! - I don 't know !
She 's got a gun !
In the elevator .
Hey ! Goddam tourist !
Come on !
Hey , watch were you 're going .
Hey buddy .
Can I borrow your car ?
My car .. !
Come on honey , let 's get out of here .
Yeah ?
- I 'm tired ... - Just keep running !
I can 't run anymore .. !
Hey Joe ! Snake !
How are you , big guy ?
Hi Max , how are you doing ?
Let 's kick some ass !
You guys stand by the old control tower .
Okay Tub . Snake , get the panzer .
Yeah , you got it .
Erica , stay here .
Charge !
Fuckin ' A !
All right !
Yeah !
Let 's teach her a lesson .
Yeah , yeah !
Attack !
Yeah !
Fuck you .
Eat shit .
I 'm outta here .
Now Joe , blow her off !
Yeah , eat it you bitch !
Let 's go home now , honey .
Yeah .
That should be enough to kill anybody .
Max , look !
What the hell ?
Holy Moses !
- Snake ! - Watch out .
Snake !
Come on , man !
So long , buddy .
Tub ... My buddy .
Die motherfucker !
God dammit , what does it take to kill you anyway ?
Forward on , she 's getting tired !
Go on up .
No !
Go on .
Max !
All right , you witch . Come on !
Come on .
You 're going to hell , you bitch !
Hi Tom .
Did you have a rough day ?
Shit ...
You 're still alive , man ?
Sure , you think that thing could kill me ?
You know what ?
What ?
I wanna live
forever .
The struggle within our souls is never-ending .
The life of man , short and brutal .
Torn between good and evil .
Of the eternity around us -
we know nothing .
The stars look on .
They have been here long before mankind appeared on our small planet -
and will be here long after we are no more .
Subtitles by Shotgun Ramadan